Whenever I have a holiday, I
remember only two things.  Either shopping or
cooking, but today I did both the things together.  I got
ready quickly and this was my
outfit for today.  Then we left the house.
First of all I saw some clothes but I did
not like anything particularly.  Meanwhile it started raining
so we quickly returned home.  As soon as I reach home,
my mother demands that
something tasty should be prepared in such a lovely weather.
Where are you going to leave such opportunities?  First, I mixed semolina,
curd and spices and
kept it aside for 10 minutes and on the other side, I
started beating it and chopping the veggies.  That's why I feel like
trying something tasty every holiday.  Then put that batter
on the pan and top it with wedges.  Actually, I was
trying this for the first time.  Our
semolina upma was also ready.  Now it was time to
test it.  They were really very yummy.
With this, we will meet in the next blog.  Bye bye.